gsnrecipes.com 2003-06-26

# GSN Recipe Solutions

## **Privacy Information**

**GSN** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for our website, **gsnrecipes.com**. 

We log your IP address, browser type, access time, operating system, immediately prior site address, page views and click-thrus, and search criteria and results to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer and revise the site and to gather broad non-identifying demographic information. 

**gsnrecipes.com** uses cookies to keep track of and facilitate your purchases on our site and to keep track of your login name and recipe search preferences. You cannot use the site if your browser does not accept cookies. 

**gsnrecipes.com's** registration forms require you to give us contact information (like your name and email address) and optional demographic information (like your gender). We use your contact information to send you information about our website. The contact information is also used to contact you when necessary to resolve a service-related problem. You may opt-out of receiving future e-mail; see the choice/opt-out section below. We also collect your city/town of birth as a security measure, to be used as verification of your identity if you forget your password. 

Personal profile data like your cookbook and dietary preferences is also collected by **gsnrecipes.com**. We use this data to tailor your experience at our site by showing you recipes according to your stated preferences and store it for your benefit on future visits. The personally identifiable parts of this information are not shared with any outside party. Non-identifying demographic and profile information, however, is shared with advertisers, business partners and investors on an aggregate basis. 

**Public Forums**

**gsnrecipes.com** makes chat rooms, forums and message boards available to its users. A third party who works closely with **gsnrecipes.com** coordinates the chat area of the site. **gsnrecipes.com** shares registration information with this party in order to help her plan chat programming but she does not share this information with any outside parties. Your email address provided on our "Ask the Chef" page is used for a one time only response to your question. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Security**

This site has industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information from you which is under our control. Access to sensitive data such as your credit card number is limited to as few employees or subcontractors as possible. We encrypt the transmission of confidential information over public communication lines and at our site using SSL (secure sockets layer) technology. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**

**gsnrecipes.com** provides you with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request registration information. You can change this preference at any time by selecting "preferences" in the left navigational bar and then clicking on "general info" after providing your user name and password. If you would like to remove your information from our database, e-mail this request to [info@gsnrecipes.com](mailto:info@gsnrecipes.com). 

**Correct/Update**

This site gives you the following options for correcting and updating information previously provided on **gsnrecipes.com.**

  1. For registration or personal profile information, select "preferences" in the left navigational bar and then click on "general info" (after entering your user name and password). 
  2. Email [info@gsnrecipes.com](mailto:info@gsnrecipes.com). 
  3. Send mail to the following postal address: GSN, 6520 Edenvale Blvd Ste. 116, Eden Prairie, MN 55344, attn: Customer Service. 

**Changes in Use of Personally Identifiable Information**

If **gsnrecipes.com** decides to change how it uses the personally identifiable information it collects from users, the changes will be highlighted in this privacy statement and prior consent via e-mail will be obtained from users who have previously provided information. 

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: 

GSN Recipe Solutions  
888 Lumber Exchange Building  
10 South 5th St.  
Minneapolis, MN 55402  
results@gsnrecipes.com
